I dug Russell up.
Russell Edgington was the
only vampire powerful enough
to take Roman Zimojic out.
All you want is power.
No. I want to share it.
Only thing that matters
is what's in your heart right now.
Do you hate
Jessica Hamby?
I do.
Who would want
to kill shifters?
Who even knows
about shifters?
You killed my friends.
He was telling me
that there's this spirit
made of smoke
that's hunting him down.
Are you gonna be able
to live with yourself
if you give up on that man?
My Jesusito,
he had a gift.
I will take back
what belongs to me.
You take this, you grow up
to be big and strong.
Emma?
I don't know you no more.
Being on V gives him
too much advantage.
I'm prepared to lose.
Your magic is finite.
You will run out
if you aren't careful
how much you use it.
- Would I be human?
- You would be fae no longer.
This is the blood of Lilith.
Nothing could be less symbolic.
Tonight, everyone
will drink from her.
I'm hungry!
Lilith.
Enjoy prison, asshole.
You think this
is all gonna stop?
There's a hundred
of me out there, shifter.
A thousand.
So sleep tight.
Shut up, butt plug.
Evening,
Mr. Merlotte.
They're everywhere.
At my house, in the hospital.
- Hey, shh.
- Goddamn maniacs.
Deep breath.
All right?
One's off to jail.
Andy'll track
down the rest.
- We are being hunted.
- Take-- take it easy.
I'm not gonna take--
There's a deputy right
outside your door.
We should start picking off these
moonshine-drinking rednecks
one by one.
See how they fucking like it.
Okay, okay.
That's not gonna solve anything.
We should get rid of them
before they get rid of us.
- You need to rest.
- Just--
Luna, hey.
All right?
- I promise you--
- Okay.
Come on, shh.
I promise-- I promise
you'll feel better.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Okay? All right.
Hey, listen.
I'm on this.
I'm headed to
the station right now.
Okay.
- Night, Mr. Merlotte.
- Night, Kevin.
Keep an eye on her.
This is fucking ridiculous.
Do nothing.
Stay in your room.
Be helpless.
Fuck me.
( theme music playing )
♪ True Blood 5x08♪
Somebody That I Used to Know
Original Air Date on July 29, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪ When you came in
the air went out ♪
♪ And every shadow
filled up with doubt ♪
♪ I don't know who
you think you are ♪
♪ But before
the night is through ♪
♪ I want to do
bad things with you ♪
♪ I'm the kind
to sit up in his room ♪
♪ Heart sick and eyes
filled up with blue ♪
♪ I don't know what
you've done to me ♪
♪ But I know
this much is true ♪
♪ I want to do
bad things with you ♪
♪ Ow, ooh ♪
♪ I want to do
real bad things with you. ♪
Oh, yes.
...fuckface!
Ride the pony,
ride the pony.
What the hell
just happened?
We saw her.
She appeared to us.
We saw Lilith.
Yeah, I saw something.
We were in
the presence of God.
We were high
as fucking kites.
Get out of me!
Get out!
Hey! Hey!
Jason!
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
You got me in the head.
What the hell's happening?
It's like
a thunderstorm out here.
I'm dumping
all my fairy light.
- Why would you wanna do that?
- Because I'm tired.
I'm tired
of hearing voices,
I'm tired of being
chased by vampires,
and I'm tired
of being a freak.
Hey.
- You are not a freak.
- That's easy for you to say.
You don't know what it's like
to be standing in line
at the bank and hear
the guy behind you
thinking about how
he wants to suck your toes.
Ew.
That happened?
You don't know what it's like to have
your parents' death on your hands
just because
of what you are.
- I wanna be normal.
- The hell you do.
Look, if you were normal,
you never woulda met Bill.
Yeah, big loss there.
Now, I know you two
had your ups and downs,
but you loved him.
Real love.
And that's something
not everyone gets.
And talking to Gran
on the other side,
hearing her voice
one last time?
That don't happen
to normal folk.
You're right.
And I'll tell
you something else.
You are who you are
'cause you got
Mama and Daddy
inside of you.
And you wanna
get rid of that
to feel normal?
And even if you did
un-fairy yourself,
it ain't ever gonna
feel right until we find out
who killed our parents.
And that thing
that you have in you,
your special power,
that could be the one thing
that could help us.
So please, don't be spraying
it all over the yard.
Hey, that thing at the bank
really happened?
It was Mike Spencer.
Ew.
Mr. Merlotte?
- How did you--
- Mind your own goddamn business!
I seen you.
You know,
they say my blood
is like a goddamn
milkshake.
You don't even need
no straw.
We witnessed
a miracle tonight.
We saw God
- and She smiled upon us.
- Unbelievable.
I mean, I have never--
The most beautiful thing
I've ever seen
in 500 years.
I never truly believed
until now.
First, may I say
God has the most beautiful
tits I've ever seen.
Now, I have never
been called devout,
but watching Lilith
shoot out of a blood pool
while I sucked down a bride
to the dulcet strains
of "You Light Up My Life",
well, praise Lilith,
praise Jesus,
praise Moses's cock!
I am born again!
Amen. Me, too.
For the first time
in a decade,
I ate a child.
I took his life inside
of me and it was ripe.
- Yes.
- This was a sign.
Roman's death has been
sanctioned by God
and we're on
the correct path.
Yes.
And now we can move forward
with a clear conscience.
But we have
a lot of work to do
and we will need food.
So, Steve, please
have the guards procure
a few dozen humans
before daybreak.
Just put them
in the holding cells.
I need a baby.
Lilith wants me
to eat a baby.
And a baby for Nigel.
Coming right up.
Well, I think I've had
enough fun for one night.
Are you coming?
You know this doesn't mean
I'm your girlfriend.
I don't remember asking.
You wanna be
my girlfriend?
Maybe.
You rang?
I thought you might wanna join me
for a late-night snack.
Please don't do this.
I have a four-month-old
daughter. Please.
Thank you, but, um,
I'm not hungry.
Who are you
to refute
God's plan?
Feed on this woman
as Lilith has commanded.
No! Please, no.
You can't do this.
Did you think the club
was an anomaly?
That we would stop
after one night?
No.
That we would starve
ourselves on Tru Blood?
- Is that what you thought?
- I will not be bullied.
Understand this.
I have fathered children.
I cannot take this woman
away from--
If you really loved
your human children,
why didn't you make
them vampire?
Keep them
with you forever?
Please.
God, no.
Miss Sarah, someone's
here to see you.
- Father?
- My angel.
Am I in heaven?
No.
But your face.
- You're so--
- I appear as you knew me
when you were a child.
So young.
It's not possible.
I have missed you
every hour of every day.
But how?
I have been shown how
to live longer
than most ever
thought possible.
Make me like you, then.
My angel, I cannot.
I don't wanna die.
- Sarah--
- Please.
I want to live.
- No.
- Why?
Immortality is a curse.
I can feel myself rotting.
No.
Please.
Please!
God chose us
to make in
His true likeness,
to transcend childish human
notions of morality.
Sick.
You're all so sick.
I have a daughter.
I have a family.
Please, I just want
to go home.
Just shut up!
To refuse
God's gift to us
is blasphemy.
No!
We thank Thee,
Lord and Lilith,
for this and all
Thy many blessings.
Whoo!
Where the hell are we?
It took us forever
to get out here.
We're home, brother.
- Mm-hmm.
- All right.
We got a surprise
for you, Hoyt.
Happy times, fellas.
Hoyt, this is
a big night for you.
Something to officially
welcome you to the group.
Hey, don't look her
in the fucking eyes, y'all. Shit.
Dipshit, this ain't
our first vamper.
Picked her up
just for you.
- Hoyt?
- You know how you was telling us
how she broke your heart?
Partly your own fault
for dating fucking death incarnate.
Yeah, well,
we got to talking.
We decided, instead of staking
the bitch ourselves,
we was gonna let you do it.
Yeah, give her some real payback
for the pain she done caused you.
You hear that, Ruby Red?
Your ex-boyfriend's gonna
stick it in you one last time.
And I mean the stake,
not your johnson.
- Yeah, I understand.
- Oh, no stake tonight.
You got six shots,
all wooden with a silver core.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Looking at her, though,
it looks like you're only
gonna probably need one.
Hey.
Don't get cold feet.
It ain't murder.
She's already fucking dead.
- I know.
- Hoyt--
Shut up! She done caused
you a world of hurt.
Not to mention
she's a fucking freak of nature.
- You!
- Yeah, I know.
You fucking hate
her dead guts, right?
- You said so.
- Yeah, it's just-- it's just--
All right, all right,
all right. All right, listen here.
Listen here.
Now, you need
to do this, brother.
It's gonna feel good.
It's gonna help you heal.
Hey.
Now...
I'm gonna lock this door
and it ain't opening
till you finish her.
Are you absolutely sure
you want to go down this path?
I didn't even know this path
existed until you told me.
"You have powers
you've never even dreamed of."
So do I?
Or was that all just bull-hockey?
Look, we just want
to find the son of a bitch
that killed our parents.
So if my sister has secret powers
that can help us,
y'all had better speak up.
Hey, do you have any idea
what it feels like
to find out that
your parents were murdered
by a freaking vampire?
You cannot come in here,
start screaming about vampires,
and just expect me
to help you.
When our kind
came to this plane,
we swore not to involve
ourselves in such matters.
- I know how we can help.
- Claudette.
- Well, I do.
- Shh. Listen.
I care about
the two of you, okay?
Our families have a bond.
We have a bond.
I don't know who killed
your parents,
but there may be a way
we can find out.
- How?
- Meet me at the bridge
where your parents were
murdered at noon.
Jesus.
- Thanks.
- For what?
Are you fucking real?
Does it matter?
I know you got friends.
Dipshits like you
grow in bunches.
Oh, it's just me,
Officer.
One man doing his best
to save America.
Save America?
From what?
Freaks.
Now listen here,
fuckstick.
I been hauling your ass
in here since high school,
but this time you're gonna go
to prison till the goddamn Rapture
unless you start talking.
I want names.
I want addresses.
And if I don't get 'em,
my Taser's gonna ask
your nuts to the big dance.
Fuck you, shifter-lover.
- Asshole.
- Andy--
Shut up, Merlotte.
I said you could observe.
Andy, hey.
Could I have a minute alone
with our friend here?
I have certain techniques.
Might help get us answers.
It's against the law.
I'm gonna go
get a cup of coffee.
Might be a while
before I get back.
It's just a matter
of time, freak.
Bang.
That's funny
'cause I was thinking
the same thing.
Whoa, whoa.
What the hell?
I ain't no fucking homo.
Neither am I.
Shit.
Fuck.
Sheriff!
What the monkey spunk?
Where's that son of a bitch
who tried to kill me?
- What?
- Is Sam here?
I mean, have you seen me?
Are you shitting me,
Merlotte?
- They hurt?
- I don't know.
Andy, they got Jessica Hamby.
I got the address--
oh, sweet Jesus.
Holy shit.
What the hell happened?
How the fuck should I know?
I was in my room and the
next thing I know, I'm you.
Jesus Christ.
All right, easy.
It's okay.
Okay?
I am fucked.
When I shift back--
Can you shift back?
Don't you think I fucking
tried that already?
- I'm gonna die, Sam.
- No, you're not gonna die.
- You'll be okay.
- No, I won't.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, fuck.
Fuck. Fuck.
I hate this goddamn town.
So, Sookie, there is
absolutely no guarantee
that what we're about
to try will work.
What are we about to try?
Everything is made of energy.
Albert Einstein--
Who was a halfling
just like you, Sookie.
--explained this to your kind
with his E equals MC squared.
Matter is simply
frozen energy.
And this energy
permeates everything.
So when something happens...
For instance,
when a woman gives birth.
...it sends ripples through the
energy that never completely die.
They can be accessed by someone
who has a connection to them.
So there's a way
to access the ripples
to see
into the past?
Fairies have
this ability, yes.
Well, ain't you glad
you didn't get rid of your light?
And since your strongest
connection is with your mother,
you'll try and inhabit
her memory.
- In essence, become her.
- Experience what she experienced,
- through her eyes.
- Here, where it occurred.
Perhaps you'll learn
the identity
of the vampire
that you seek.
My sisters and I will help
amplify the signal.
Join hands.
Okay, I want you
to concentrate, Sookie,
as though you're
reading thoughts.
Just let it come.
Oh, my God.
I can smell Mama's perfume.
Jason, I can feel her.
Are you kidding?
It's incredible.
- Corbett, no! No!
- What do you want?
Wait. Wait.
Come here!
- Help me! No!
- Get off of him!
No, we have children!
Please!
It smells
so good in here.
"It smells so good."
Stop! Warlow,
leave the girl alone!
- Sook?
- Sookie?
Hoyt?
Please.
T-take the silver off.
Ray's right.
You're already dead.
Shooting you
wouldn't be murder.
You fucked
my best friend.
You sucked his dick.
You broke
my goddamn heart.
And I fucking loved you.
I know you did.
So why don't you
love me anymore?
I wanted to love you.
I even prayed
for it to come back.
It just didn't.
It ain't never gonna.
I'm sorry.
It tries to tear him apart--
- You did it?
- Where are the other boys?
They ain't here.
There's your
fucking milkshake.
All right.
Let's go.
Wait, I can't.
It's daytime.
Oh, shit.
Well, I got no phone.
We're a hundred miles
in the middle of nowhere.
- I'll send help.
- Okay. Hey, Hoyt?
Thank you.
Fuck you, Jess.
Lafayette, thank God.
Unless y'all are here to tell me
I done goddamn won the lottery,
- get out my face.
- We need your help.
Hooker, I ain't in
the helping business no more.
I'm in the "fuck off
while I smoke a blunt" business
and business is about
to pick way the fuck up.
Lafayette, it's Terry.
I don't know if he's off his meds
or if he's just gone crazy,
but he thinks a woman
he killed in Iraq has cursed him.
Uh, tell him about
the fire monster.
Oh, also, he thinks a demon
made of fire is hunting him.
He off his meds.
Ciao, bitches.
Lafayette, please.
You and I both know
that there are things
in this world
that are beyond
explanation.
And even if
it isn't real
and Terry
is off his meds,
he still believes
it's true.
So what the fuck do
y'all want me to do?
Convince him
it's not true.
You're a medium.
Terry knows that.
So, we all sit down,
you try and make contact
with this woman's spirit,
and then you tell him
she's agreed to lift the curse.
If we can convince Terry
that her spirit
has called off the demon,
then it won't matter one lick
if it's all mumbo jumbo.
He'll be at peace.
And I can have my family back.
Look here.
I'm sick and tired
of doing this shit for free.
So if you wants my help,
you gots to pay for it.
- Are you serious?
- Mm.
Okay. 50 bucks.
300.
I'm about to slip
my ass in this tub
and get high
as a motherfucker.
Enjoys your day.
- Oh, my God. Jessica.
- Sam.
- Sam?
- That's his girlfriend.
She turned into him.
Now she's stuck.
She turned into
what?
Uh, never mind.
Who the hell's this?
Oh, uh, Reggie.
He's dead.
- Where's Hoyt?
- He's not with you?
- No. Are you okay?
- Wait, wait. Hoyt left.
He said he was
going to get help.
- Do you smell that?
- Yeah.
- What?
- Was there a woman here?
- A human woman.
- No, just guys.
- Wait-- which one of you is Sam?
- I am.
Well, there was
a woman here.
And she's a big one.
Lousy diet,
a lot of Cheetos,
Mello Yello.
Smoker, too.
Menthols.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
- What's wrong?
- Luna?
Help me. Ah!
First I was Mama.
I saw what she was seeing.
Then I was the vampire.
- I saw what he saw.
- That's impossible.
Fairies cannot make
contact with vampires.
I know. I can't even read
their thoughts.
This is--
this is fucked.
You psychically
bonded to a vampire.
Why did we even try this?
'Cause you said
it was okay.
Uh, the "special powers."
"Nature's got
a frozen memory."
- Remember?
- Yes, I know.
But I didn't think
we'd make some sort of connection
to a fucking vampire.
The elders are gonna
be furious about this.
I don't give a twirly fuck
about your elders.
What I care about
is this vampire.
So we gotta find him
and make him pay for what he did.
And we will.
We just must be cautious.
- You saw Claudine.
- Yes.
She said...
"Leave the girl alone,"
and then she zapped me.
Well, this was
a goddamn bust,
fairy boy.
Sookie had
a horrible experience,
and what'd we learn
about this vampire?
Diddly fucking squat!
Warlow,
leave the girl alone!
Warlow
Warlow.
Wait.
Claudine called me
by my name.
Not my name,
the vampire's name.
She called him Warlow.
Does Warlow
mean anything to you?
No.
But clearly Claudine
knew who he was.
Strawberry daiquiri.
Tara.
Oh, my God.
- Tara Thornton.
- Tracy.
When is the last time
I saw you? High school?
Yeah, I guess.
Well, how are you?
- That's how.
- Oh, my God.
You're a vampire.
That's crazy.
Now you're a member
of two minorities.
Well, I see you haven't
changed at all.
Still sticking
your fat foot in your mouth.
- Beg your pardon?
- Hmm?
Nothing.
Shoot, I am just
so relieved to see you
holding down
a steady job.
I know your mama
used to drink, so...
It's nice seeing you.
Here's your drink.
Nice seeing you, too.
I didn't order this.
- I said vodka tonic.
- You said strawberry daiquiri.
Well, it's fine.
Never mind.
If you're too lazy
to fix your own mistake...
What did you just say?
Jeez, you're the same
as you were in high school.
- All uppity.
- Uppity?
Listen,
you white trash fucktwat.
We're not
in high school anymore.
So if you let any more
of that racist bullshit
fall out of your mouth,
I'm gonna rip open
your heart and fry it up
with some grits
and collard greens.
Tara.
Ma'am, I apologize.
Tara's new and stupid.
Your drink's
on the house.
Thank you.
- I've known Tara since high school.
- Hmm.
Even back then, she had trouble
connecting with folks.
I connected with your boyfriend
well enough to fuck him.
Well, I don't live
in the past, Tara.
I live in the present.
In a four-bedroom house
with a BMW in the garage.
So enjoy your little job,
barkeep.
Fuck you.
Tara, that's enough.
Don't you get uppity
with me, y'hear?
Shreveport pack,
let's make some noise.
All right.
Now, y'all know
our leader,
Marcus Bozeman,
has fallen.
It is time for
a new Packmaster to rise!
Come on!
Now, our first challenger
is a lifelong member
of the Shreveport pack.
He has been a mentor
to many of us.
He's raised nine wolves,
and was the godfather
to Marcus Bozeman himself.
Let's hear it
for J.D. Carson.
Our next challenger is a
relative newcomer to our pack,
but his strength
is already legendary.
He is a son of a former
Jackson, Mississippi, Packmaster.
Let's hear it
for Alcide Herveaux!
- Pussy!
- Yay, Alcide!
Y'all know the drill.
Candidates, either
in wolf or human form,
will track, capture,
and kill the quarry animal.
What are we hunting?
A deer? Wild boar?
No, no, no, no.
Thank you.
Tonight, we're gonna
harken back to our forebearers.
It's time to bring tradition
and integrity back to this pack.
Now, I know some of you
may think this is unfair.
And lest you think that this
ain't much of a challenge,
this young man
is a track star at the university.
And we're
gonna hunt as men,
not wolves.
But we will give him a very
sportsmanlike two-minute head start.
Please, please. My dad's a
councilman. He'll give you anything.
So, what? You're gonna kill
an innocent kid
just to prove that you can run
faster than some track star
while you're on V?
- Right.
- Shut up.
I ain't gonna stand around
and watch this happen.
Wait.
You can't drop out.
If it saves
that kid's life,
that's exactly
what I'm gonna do.
Well, all righty then.
I think we got us
a forfeit.
All right, all right.
Tell you what, though.
Just to make it official,
I'm still gonna
hunt this boy down.
Get running!
You're a drug addict and
you're a disgrace to all wolves.
Now you're fixing
to add murder to the list?
You ain't fit to lead this pack,
you jacked up piece of shit.
And you ain't fit to wipe my ass.
Go get him!
Brother.
This isn't you, Nora.
- It's insane.
- Insane?
I have loved you
for nearly 600 years.
And I've loved you.
But this place,
all of-- all of this,
and this?
It's clouded your mind.
Eric, Lilith blesses
this place.
Lilith doesn't exist.
Salome chose
this path for you.
Eric, Lilith does exist.
You saw her.
You were there.
Yes, I was.
And so was Godric.
And it sickened him.
Godric?
The night he turned you,
the night he made us
a family,
I swore to him that
I would always protect you.
And tonight he reminded
me of that promise.
Eric,
we both loved Godric.
He gave us the most
magnificent gift.
And when he made us,
he was as pure a vampire
as I've ever known.
Salome's strength and vision
would have delighted him.
It doesn't.
It sickens him.
It's not Salome
who's sick.
Do you remember Godric at the end
when he'd lost his way?
The Godric you say you saw
last night was a perversion.
- How can you say that?
- Because it's true.
In his final days,
Godric was a blasphemer,
a weak,
disgusting apologist
whom Lilith herself would
have been overjoyed to stake.
What's happening to you?
Fuck Godric.
Lilith will
show you the way.
I got you.
- I'm not gonna make it.
- You are.
I feel like I'm dying.
Hey, you're not
gonna die.
You got too much
to live for.
Emma needs you.
I need you.
- You hate me.
- Hate you?
You called me
a psycho.
Yeah, I did.
But you deserved it.
Maybe I did.
I can be a hothead.
Me, too.
We're a lot alike,
Sam Merlotte.
I'd say that's
an understatement.
I'm sorry.
About everything.
Me, too.
You mean more to me
than anything.
And you're
incredibly handsome.
You, too.
Luna? Baby?
Hey.
Hey, you're okay.
You okay?
We need to talk
about your attitude.
I got to make this dude
a margarita first.
You don't want
a margarita.
You want a flat,
half-empty beer.
Now.
This is yours.
After the shit she was slinging,
she owes you.
Thought you were mad.
You don't know me
that well.
My mad face
and my happy face are the same.
You are worthless.
Your only purpose
is to serve Tara Thornton.
You will worship Tara.
Everything about her
is a revelation.
You exist only
for Tara's nourishment.
You will consider
it a privilege
to let your racist
peckerwood blood
shoot into her
gorgeous cocos mouth.
You are an unpaid
food whore.
A slave.
And Tara
is your master.
Have fun.
Feed on me, please.
You're so beautiful.
I don't even deserve
to be near you.
I want your blood.
Drink it all.
It belongs to you.
Fucking-a.
Nice try, college boy.
Think you're hot shit,
don't ya?
Run.
I am done with you,
you self-righteous fuck.
- J.D., don't!
- Oh, my God.
You have won.
For the good of this pack,
please don't.
This son of a bitch
killed your son.
This is no way to begin your tenure,
by murdering your challenger.
Killing him only
tarnishes the whole pack.
How can you
stand up for him?
I am standing up
for all of us,
including you.
You are better
than this.
At least,
you used to be.
Please, J.D.
Find yourself
a new pack.
Let's celebrate.
- Yeah.
- Come on, now.
- Arlene, where's the fire?
- Okay.
- Where's the goddamn fire?
- There ain't no fire.
- What's this?
- Please sit down.
- Both of you.
- You lied to me?
- Arlene, I can't be here.
- No. No, wait--
Patrick and I
are a goddamn danger
- to everybody around. We're cursed.
- Shh.
What if we could help
you break that curse?
Look, just blow out
them goddamn candles first.
- All right.
- Okay, okay.
- Yeah.
- Okay?
Come on.
It's okay.
All right.
Now, look. I've never
been in combat.
I can't imagine what
y'all had to face in Iraq.
Now, we all know how
this started, okay?
And we're gonna
help end it.
Now, I'm here
to make contact
with the woman
y'all done killed
to see if she'll
call off the, um--
The ifrit.
Yeah.
Let's join hands.
- Mm.
- Oh, this is bullshit.
No, it's not. He's for real.
I've seen it.
Mm, I hear a noise.
Now, lady they done killed,
Terry and...
- Patrick.
- ...Patrick...
are some good men.
Now go ahead
and leave them alone, now. Mm.
So say I.
They're real, real sorry
about what
they done done.
Yeah, they is.
Ooh.
Oh, shit.
What?
She here
for fucking real.
Um, her name is Zaafira.
She pissed.
And she don't wanna forgive
either one of y'all.
- Lafayette.
- I ain't playing.
She is talking to me
and she is fucking mad.
Like I said.
Bullshit.
Holy fuck.
Whoa.
You smell that?
Ozone.
You get that when spirits breach
the corporeal plane.
She crying.
Someone blow out
them goddamn candles.
I feel an electrical charge.
- This is definitely spirit activity.
- Hold on, hold on.
Spirit's saying
she'll lift the curse--
- She will?
- Dear Lord, thank God.
She'll lift the curse if...
Oh, fuck me.
Terry, baby,
you got to kill Patrick.
Or either
he got to kill you.
What?
One of us
has got to die.
Whoo-hoo.
Hey, whoo.
Oh, thank God.
A friendly face.
I've been
so freaking lost.
I'm coming for you.
You are mine.
Gentlemen.
Join us.
It's time to start flexing
our muscles around the globe.
To start crushing
the mainstreamers.
Nora.
Mainstream is
a global problem, of course,
but we have to start
dismantling it locally.
We've several high-ranking members
of the British Parliament
who are willing
to help us in the UK.
And Russia.
We have friends
in the Duma.
They'd be more than happy
to round up the mainstreamers,
stick 'em on a raft
in the Black Sea at high noon.
- Have you ever been to Hong Kong?
- Nuh-uh.
But I loved
kung pao chicken.
Hmm. It's the most
wonderful place on earth.
Asian men with British accents
giving you a shiatsu rubdown
and you feel like
James Bond--
Steve. Russell?
Yes, my pet?
We are working here.
Oh, well, we're all ears,
sugar lumps.
What about bankrolling gangs
of vigilantes
willing to stake
mainstreamers on sight?
We have ample resources
in our treasury.
Let's talk about the U.S.
Tru Blood.
Excuse me?
- Tru Blood.
- Tru Blood?
Fuck politics.
Concentrate
on the Tru-Blood.
What about it?
You bomb the factories.
There are only
five of them.
Destroy them publicly
and you force mainstreamers
to feed on humans.
As they were meant to.
- Well done.
- That's genius.
- Yes.
- I love it.
- What are you doing?
- Evolving.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪ I had tender feelings
that you made hard ♪
♪ But it's your heart,
not mine, that's scarred ♪
♪ So when I go home,
I'll be happy to go ♪
♪ You're just somebody
that I used to know ♪
♪ You don't need
my help anymore ♪
♪ It's all now to you,
there ain't no before ♪
♪ Now that you're big enough
to run your own show ♪
♪ You're just somebody
that I used to know. ♪